export const course3Assignments = [
	{
		_id: '63f1a2e8e8a1a1a1a1a1a1e5',
		coursId: '63f1a2e8e8a1a1a1a1a1a1a6',
		questions: [
			{
				question:
					'Which of the following is a primary color in design?',
				options: ['Red', 'Orange', 'Green', 'Purple'],
				correctOption: 'Red'
			},
			{
				question:
					'What is the purpose of white space in graphic design?',
				options: [
					'To fill empty areas',
					'To create a balanced and uncluttered design',
					'To make the design look busy',
					'To add more elements to the design'
				],
				correctOption: 'To create a balanced and uncluttered design'
			},
			{
				question: 'What does RGB stand for in color theory?',
				options: [
					'Red, Green, Blue',
					'Red, Gray, Black',
					'Red, Gold, Blue',
					'Ruby, Green, Blue'
				],
				correctOption: 'Red, Green, Blue'
			},
			{
				question:
					'Which tool is commonly used for vector-based graphic design?',
				options: ['Photoshop', 'Illustrator', 'InDesign', 'Lightroom'],
				correctOption: 'Illustrator'
			},
			{
				question: "What is the 'rule of thirds' in design?",
				options: [
					'A technique for aligning elements to create visual balance',
					'A rule for using only three colors in a design',
					'A layout for dividing the design into three equal parts',
					'A method for organizing text into three sections'
				],
				correctOption:
					'A technique for aligning elements to create visual balance'
			},
			{
				question: 'What does CMYK stand for in color printing?',
				options: [
					'Cyan, Magenta, Yellow, Black',
					'Cyan, Magenta, Yellow, White',
					'Color, Model, Yellow, Black',
					'Cyan, Model, Yellow, Black'
				],
				correctOption: 'Cyan, Magenta, Yellow, Black'
			},
			{
				question: 'Which file format is best for web graphics?',
				options: ['JPEG', 'PNG', 'TIFF', 'GIF'],
				correctOption: 'PNG'
			},
			{
				question: 'What is a vector graphic?',
				options: [
					'A graphic made of pixels',
					'A graphic that can be scaled without losing quality',
					'A graphic with a fixed resolution',
					'A graphic that uses raster images'
				],
				correctOption:
					'A graphic that can be scaled without losing quality'
			},
			{
				question:
					'Which of the following is a key principle of good typography?',
				options: [
					'Using multiple fonts',
					'Ensuring readability and legibility',
					'Using only one color',
					'Using complex font styles'
				],
				correctOption: 'Ensuring readability and legibility'
			},
			{
				question:
					'What is the main purpose of a mood board in graphic design?',
				options: [
					'To create a color palette',
					'To gather visual inspiration and ideas',
					'To outline the project budget',
					'To sketch initial designs'
				],
				correctOption: 'To gather visual inspiration and ideas'
			}
		],
		submitted: false,
		score: null
	}
];
